Excuse me, sir. Sir, question for you.
Yeah.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yes.
What do you do for living out here
in Austin to be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I'm in software.
I'm an investor.
So you're in finance?
Yeah, private equity and venture capital. Absolutely.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Well, I sold my company for 800 million.
For how much?
800 million.
You sold a company for 800 million?
What type of company did you sell?
Braintree Venmo. Have you ever paid somebody with Venmo?
Like Venmo, the app?
Do you think I could interview you real quick?
I have one of the biggest
business media channels in the entire world.
I go all over interviewing the most successful people.
I think I've heard of you guys.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'd love to talk to you.
Would you want me to interview you? Is that cool?
That would be awesome.
Awesome.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
We're over $850 million in revenue.
Over $850 million?
Yeah.
So, through the grace of God, the companies that have started
do well in excess of $1 billion in revenue every year.
You're doing $1 billion in revenue a year?
Yes, I absolutely do.
Your last message to somebody in their 20s
trying to build a billion-dollar company in today's world.
They want to become successful like you.
You've heard the saying that everything's bigger in Texas,
but I don't think you realize how
big, I mean wealthy, it actually is.
It actually is out here.
In fact, Texas is home to over 80 billionaires.
And if Texas was its own country, it would
be the eighth largest economy in the entire world.
So, I flew out to Texas today in Austin, which
is home to billionaires like Elon Musk and Michael Dell,
to go around finding and asking some of
these billionaires what they did to become wealthy
and how you watching can become financially free and follow
in their footsteps to become millionaires and billionaires in today's world.
This video is about to be insane
from start to finish, so stay tuned.
And with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
So, let's get this video on the way.
Let's get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Question for you.
Yeah.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yes.
Yes, it is.
What do you do for living out here
in Austin to be able to afford a G-Wagon?
I am an entrepreneur.
I make smoothies for a living.
You sell smoothies?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
13 years.
Over these 13 years, what's the most amount
of money that you've made in a single year?
I think last year we did 23 million.
This year we'll do between 32 and 35 million.
35 million?
Yeah.
When I go all over the world, I
grew a channel to 12 million followers, interviewing the
most successful business owners.
Can we get one minute with
you for our channel real quick?
Yeah, fuck.
I see you on Instagram.
I love you.
Don't you think everybody's built for entrepreneurship?
No, not everybody's built for entrepreneurship.
Listen, there's two types of people on this planet.
People that talk shit and people that do shit.
If you talk shit, you're
going to be a miserable motherfucker.
If you do shit, you're
going to have a good life.
So, you're going to be an action taker.
You've got to be an action taker and
you've got to speak life onto people, compliment
people, build them up.
Fuck all this cancel culture shit.
Somebody deserves a compliment, you give them a compliment.
Don't flatter people.
Never flatter people because it's creepy and it'll
come back to bite you in the ass.
If you put your faith in God, miracles will happen.
Doors will open.
Shit that you never in a million fucking
years could imagine will take place in your life.
Have you seen miracles happen?
Oh my God.
Dude, I went from living under a fucking
bridge 21 years ago, addicted to heroin and crack,
and now drive a fancy car, got a fancy business.
So what was that turning point
in your life into financial freedom?
First of all, you've got to surrender.
Once you surrender.
You're willing your life over, over to God.
Then you got to take responsibility for
everything that's going on in your life.
Good and bad.
So like my whole thing was I was a victim.
I spent 33 years on
this planet as a fucking victim.
My parents were bad.
I got molested.
My teachers were bad.
I got kicked out of high school.
I'm a fucking loser.
I'm a high school dropout.
I'm a convicted felon.
It was just this perpetual tape of
victimhood and it was everybody else's fault.
The moment I took autonomy over myself, once
I finally conceded to my innermost self that
everything going on in my life was my fault.
Not my parents' fault.
Not the fucking school that kicked me out.
It was my fault.
Once you take responsibility for yourself and you
ask God with all your heart to help
you, there's nothing you can't do.
I started at 33, homeless and fucking penniless.
I washed dogs.
I cleaned houses.
I washed cars.
I did whatever the fuck I could
do because I couldn't get a job.
Nobody would hire me.
I looked like shit, but I did
whatever the fuck I had to do.
I worked seven days a week.
Make more money than you spend.
Invest that fucking money.
Save that money.
Invest that money and just ask God for help.
And honestly, for the young men out there.
Don't look at that porn.
Stop pounding your fucking carrot every day.
That's your life force.
Put that shit away.
That will rob you of your
soul just like the dope will.
Your last message to the younger generation.
What's the best advice you could give to
any 20 year old watching this right now?
Young men out there, take care of your mom.
Take care of your mom.
Call her every day and tell her you love her.
I wish I could call my mom
right now and tell her I love her.
She's gone, but I spoiled the shit out of
my mom the last 17 years of her life.
Jewelry, vacations, house, everything.
That's the highest level of manhood
is taking care of your mom.
I know she's a pain in the ass.
I know she pushes your buttons.
I know she drives you nuts.
That's what they're supposed to do.
They're your fucking mother.
Take care of your mom.
That was fucking fire.
Thank you.
That was incredible.
Thank you so much for your time, sir.
Yeah, man.
Guys, that was one of
my favorite conversations I've ever had.
He got rich.
I mean rich off of selling smoothies.
His business is going to do $30 million this
year, but he just gave us some of the best
life advice I've ever heard, especially towards the
end of that interview when he said, fellas,
take care of your mom.
At the end of the day, the most important
thing that you can do is take care of your
family and never give up on them.
Great interview out here in Austin.
But we got to go
get this next one, you guys.
Come on, let's go.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes.
Question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
Well, how old was I
when I made my first million?
What line of business are you in?
What line of business am I in now?
I'm an investor.
So you're in finance.
Yeah.
Private equity and venture capital.
Absolutely.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
A lot of money.
Could you give me a range?
So through the grace of God, the companies I
started do well in excess of a billion dollars
of revenue every year.
Are you serious?
Yes.
You're doing a billion dollars in revenue a year?
The companies that I started, yes, absolutely do.
What's the best industry somebody
can get into in today's world?
Oh, gosh.
Gosh.
There are a lot of great ones.
Give me the number one right now.
I'm going to redefine the term industry.
Africa.
Here's the story.
Follow me on this.
Nine of the 20 fastest growing economies in the
world are going to be in Africa in 2025.
Everybody's overlooking it.
Only 0.5% of the world's private equity
and venture capital is going into Africa, despite
the fact that it's going to be
the only continent with a growing population.
A marketplace is all about consumers and producers instead
of people on the tail end of life that
are draining money out of the economy.
Africa has a vibrancy.
They're able to just step
over the traditional landline telecom.
Their technology, they're digital natives.
They're growing.
They've got incredible work ethic.
They've got stable democracies now in many cases.
Africa, as an industry, as a concept,
is the most overlooked, undervalued investment opportunity
for entrepreneurs and investors right now in 2025.
Let me ask you this.
Yeah, bring it.
What was your secret to
scaling to a billion dollar company?
I got to know the guys at Chick-fil-A really well.
Okay?
And theesteem.
Our business really went up.
I mean, it was the perfect裝.
Want a kicker?
We're a boomerang business where everyone was looking
out for you and you just threw the
stick down and started cosas on them.
We're winning Steel and Steel as men.
Just sitting at the één ama.
Come on.
That place wasn't ideal righteously
in the last week or so.
Absolutely not.
So let me ask you again.
Where did you land?
Thank goodness.
Can I say this?
In Obama.
Okay.
Coincidentally, we really had one guy whohad
a factor from a rib of Burenski.
Now, I think we're going to go to Obama.
That's right, not in Olga.
No, not at hail.
You delight your employee, give them
an opportunity to flourish and to thrive.
Just solving real customer issues and working on
real red meat to be able to chew on.
When you do that, they'll stick with you.
You take care of your employees,
they take care of your customers.
But your best ideas are going to come
from your customers that are taking care of those
employees.
I'm not smart enough to have enough good
ideas about how my business needs to thrive and
flourish and pivot and make all
the decisions I need to make.
I need to rely on my company employees.
You see, when they feel like they're in
a safe environment where they can thrive and
flourish and work on really important work,
they're thinking about how to do it better.
If instead, they're thinking about how do
I get another paycheck from someplace else,
then I've lost that competitive mojo.
You take care of your employees, you love
them, you understand their story and who they
are and what makes them tick, they'll stick
with you and you'll have a business that'll
thrive.
Now you guys see why
they say everything's bigger in Texas.
This video is off to a crazy start so far,
but I want to be real with you guys for a
second.
So in the last four years, I've been able
to grow this channel to over 13 million followers
across social media and
build a multi-million dollar business.
At the exact same time.
But I want to be very clear with you all.
It didn't happen because of me alone.
It's the incredible team I have behind me.
From my two other co-founders to my
editors, my videographers, to even the strategists.
Everyone plays a crucial role and they do
things I could never do on my own.
And if you're a business owner, you know how hard
it is to build a team that you can depend
on.
And that's why tools like ZipRecruiter are game changers.
ZipRecruiter's powerful matching technologies helps you
find the right candidates as fast
as possible.
They even let you send
personalized invites to top candidates.
So that way you don't miss the perfect fit.
And right now you can try it
for free at ZipRecruiter.com slash hard knocks.
So hire experienced people who are
excited about what they do with ZipRecruiter.
And you want to know something crazy?
Four to five employers who post on ZipRecruiter
get a quality candidate within the first day.
So see for yourself and
go to ZipRecruiter.com slash hard knocks.
ZipRecruiter, the smartest way to hire.
Now, with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
How old were you when you made your first million?
A million or a billion?
You made a billion.
Well, I sold my company for 800 million.
For how much?
800 million.
You sold a company for 800 million?
I did.
And I go all over the world
interviewing the most successful entrepreneurs on how they
made it for the younger generation.
Could we get one minute with
you for our channel real quick?
Sure.
What type of company did you sell?
Payments.
Braintree Venmo.
Have you ever paid somebody with Venmo?
Like Venmo, the app?
You sold Venmo?
Yes.
Actually, could we ask you a couple of quick questions?
Sure.
How long have you been a business owner?
When I was 21, I determined that I was
going to try to make a difference in the world,
doing something interesting for the human race.
And I thought entrepreneurship was a path.
I didn't know what to do.
So I thought making a bunch
of money would be a good solution.
And then when I made the money, I
would figure out what to do in my life.
How old are you now?
Over these 47 years, if you can think
about one piece of advice that you've received that
maybe helped you in business or even outside
of business, what's the best advice you ever
got throughout your career?
It would be the advice I would give to myself.
The advice I never received.
Make health your number one life priority.
And there's always a story in entrepreneurship
where you grind as hard as you can.
You'll hear stories of the person who slept
under their desk or coded for two nights in
a row.
It's like amazing.
They're epic.
But you never hear the story like
the person's well-rested and has really great biomarkers
and a clear head.
And so I wish I would have received
the advice, make health your number one life priority,
because if you do, you'll be a better entrepreneur.
And I really miss that.
I really, I traded health for wealth
and it hurt my ability to create wealth.
And there's that saying that I love that a
rich man wants a thousand things, but a sick
man only wants one thing and that's their health.
Let me ask you this.
What is your most controversial opinion about health
that a lot of people may disagree with
you on?
Something that is normalized in society.
What's your most controversial opinion
about health in today's world?
That we are the first generation that won't die.
What do you mean?
We are the first generation who will not die.
Like die?
And like actually.
That's right.
So you don't plan on dying?
How old realistically do you think you can live until?
I'm chronologically 47, but biologically, you
know, my cardiovascular ability is age
My lung capacity is age 18.
My telomeres, my endocromazones are age 18.
So my body functions in many
ways like an 18 year old.
And so when you start measuring the biological
age of your body, it's very different than
the time that you were born.
So that's what I wish I would have learned.
Typically people perform very well in their youth.
There's skill sets.
There's physical ability, mental ability, emotional ability.
That peaks typically in like early life stages.
And then it declines with older stages.
Especially that's true if you're grinding very hard.
And so this is why I say making health
your top priority, because if you do so, you're
going to be in peak performance.
Like the difference between being healthy
and non-healthy when you're thinking is like
night and day.
And so that's why I think being an
entrepreneur, making health your top priority is the highest
yield thing you can do for your company.
So you said that you're 47, but you
have the cardiovascular endurance or capacity of an
18 year old.
So are you like reverse aging?
Yeah, I guess you could say.
You're slowing down the progression
of how you can do it.
So you can do two things.
One is you can reverse aging damage.
You can slow down speed of aging.
So my speed of aging currently
is the slowest in the entire world.
So there's 5,000 people all over the
world competing for the lowest possible speed of
aging.
We call ourselves rejuvenation Olympics.
And I'm number one in the world on doing this.
So my birthday happens every 24 months.
And so I've made a new Olympic sport out
of how to slow down your speed of aging.
So anyways, I'm an entrepreneur again.
I'm trying to create a brand new sport.
And the new sport is don't die.
It's like we are the first generation who won't die.
If you take that path, what do you do?
Like you want to slow down your speed of aging.
You want to reverse aging damage.
And you want your body to operate
basically functionally like, you know, 18 year olds.
Now I'm 22 years old.
My original goal was to
live until about 80 years old.
I was like, hey, that's good.
Let's say I want to live to 100.
What's the number one thing I should be doing
right now on a daily basis to make that happen?
First, those are rookie numbers.
Yeah.
Yeah, seriously.
So the ambition we can have as a species
right now, there's no reason why we couldn't think
in the hundreds or even thousands of years.
If you just look at the speed at
which AI is improving and medical advancements are coming
over the coming decades, we'll
be able to extend our lifespans.
Like for example, like right now,
my birthday happens every two years.
I've slowed down my speed of aging.
That buys us a lot of time to find
a lot of advancements to extend life further and further.
And so I'd say for you, the three things
I would say is sleep is your number one life
priority.
Nothing's more important than sleep.
That's incredible.
Do you think America's trying to kill us?
I will tell you, I've tested over
the years, everything I put into my body.
So all the air I breathe, all the food I
eat, all the water I drink, and the world is toxic.
Like it's, you've probably heard this, but
when you see the data, it's terrifying.
Give me an example for people that
really don't know, like, like how toxic,
like maybe the little things.
Like the water we drink or just something
that you think would surprise a lot of people.
I mean, everything.
So we just started testing a bunch of stuff.
So like common things like foods you buy
in packages, they have heavy metals like mercury,
cadmium, arsenic, lead.
They have agrochemicals like glyphosate.
So everything you eat has
chemicals and very few companies test.
So we've been testing everything.
It's really contaminated.
We just tested a diaper just because we
were trying to figure out it has these dangerous
levels of glyphosate, this chemical.
We tested dog food, has high levels of mercury.
And so it really is in all the food supply.
And so we're now working on trying to source
our own foods, test them all for all these
chemicals and try to have a pure food
source, which I've done for myself, trying to make
it available to others.
But these are the kinds of
things you need to nail down.
You just don't realize every day
how exposed you are to contamination.
I know that you said that
your goal is to live forever.
And you brought up how me wanting
to live to 100 is rookie numbers.
That's right.
How old do you think you possibly can live until?
Give me a number, an estimate.
I don't think we'll die.
You don't think you will die?
No.
I mean, on the time spans, which our
minds can comprehend right now, Earth has existed
for 3.4 billion years or more.
Yeah.
I think of our lifespans on 70 years, like thereabouts.
Why?
Like, why couldn't it be a few hundred?
Why could there's already biology
already has a few immortal species.
So we know biology can achieve immortality.
We just have to take from one species
over to our species so it can be done.
It's not like we're talking about trying to
exceed the speed of light, you know, where
it's like a major physics problem.
So it can't be done.
That's why I'm saying that there's no reason
why we should have some kind of tempered expectations
or ambitions.
Right.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thanks.
I appreciate that.
Yeah.
All right, you guys.
So we just ran into an interview.
Brian Johnson, who sold his company.
For $800 million.
But that was not a
typical school of hard knocks interview.
So I'm always talking about business and
wealth building and how these millionaires and billionaires
make their money.
We talked about the most important thing that
we have that we don't even realize, which
is our health.
You see, remember a rich man wants a thousand
things, but a sick man only wants one and
that's their health.
Great interview with Brian Johnson.
He just gave us some serious value and gold
in that last interview, but we got to keep
this one rolling and go get another one out here.
You guys come on, let's go.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Question for you.
Yes.
How old were you when you made your first?
Million.
Me personally, not the business.
Yeah.
Personally.
What line of business are you in?
I'm in software.
Yeah.
And do you think I could interview real quick?
I have one of the biggest
business media channels in the entire world.
I go all over interviewing the most successful people.
I think I've heard of you guys.
Yeah.
I'd love to.
Would you remember with you?
Is that cool?
That would be awesome.
Awesome.
How long have you been a business owner?
This particular company, almost 20 years.
And I had one before that for about six.
What was the turning point?
Like getting into software.
Did you always know that you were going to
pursue software or like, how did you end up
in this business?
So I started in tech as a young man.
And in my case, that was 40 years ago in
IBM, which is a big tech firm that we all still
know.
But I didn't kind of move towards software
until I was in the industry about 15 years
and then came to Austin
to work for a company here.
Kind of got the bug of the startup game.
And then three other buddies
and I started one in 2000.
That was our first company.
Absolutely.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
The company?
Yeah.
We're over $850 million in revenue.
Over $850 million?
Yes.
What was the best advice
you ever received throughout your career?
The most pivotal, life-changing advice?
The most pivotal advice that
you received in business or anything?
What was the best advice you ever got?
I'm going to hesitate to say this is the
only great piece of advice I got, but I've given
this piece of advice to a
lot of people in business setting.
And an older guy, when I joined IBM in
the 1980s, said, look, my advice to younger folks
is to spend about 90% of your time
on your job and 10% on your career.
And I'm like, what does that mean?
And he said, look, if you spend 100% on
your job, you're going to do a really good job
at the job you're in, but nobody's ever
going to see you moving beyond that job because
you aren't making connections.
You're not thinking beyond it.
Wow.
How do you, where do you go next?
On the other hand, if you drop it to like
80, 20, spend 80% on your job and 20% run
around your career, you're not going
to do a good enough job.
You only put an 80%.
So he's like, the right balance is put
most, all of your energy, 90-ish plus percent into
doing a great job with where you're at, but
you always want to reserve like 10% of your
capacity, make connections, learn about what it
takes to go to the next level.
How do I become an entrepreneur
if I've never been an entrepreneur?
How do I get into that
industry if I'm in another industry?
You're always thinking about stretching
and growing, but that's about 10%.
And if you keep that balance, I
think that's a really healthy piece of advice.
You sold hundreds of millions
of dollars in the tech industry.
Somebody wants to break into the tech industry right now.
Give them a hack to sell
their product at a large scale.
I think to be fair in my case, and
again, we're selling that kind of dollars to large
scale companies.
So we're selling to big businesses.
So you're selling to big businesses.
So in other words, you've got
to solve those $100,000 million problems.
That's where I was going.
And you've got to have
people to know what they're doing.
That's where I was going.
Like you've got to have software
engineers, you've got to have salespeople, marketers
that understand that large business environment
because it's very different from small business,
which is different from consumer.
But so you said you're selling to tech giants though.
Oh yeah.
We're selling to the biggest companies in the world.
Like what?
Like the Fortune 500.
Half of them are our customers.
Yeah.
So when you're approaching them, when you're
selling to them, what does that conversation
look like?
How do you sell to a tech giant?
Well, you know what?
It's not one conversation.
Our sales cycles can be a year or longer
and it can be 50 people in the organization that
we got to talk to.
What is the biggest thing that the deal depends on?
Well, ultimately, and it's a team decision
typically on the customer side, it's going
to come down to, do
they believe we're the best partner?
I'll use that term, the best
company that's going to solve their problems.
And if they don't believe that, they're not
going to spend the millions of dollars to
buy your product.
So how do you effectively communicate
that when you're in a conversation?
You got to show them.
There's proving it by showing them.
Often there's these things called proofs of
concept or pilot where you're showing them
the tech.
You got to have typically very strong references.
They got to go, I want to see
five other people like me that already use this.
So the hardest part of a business like ours
is the early days when you don't have those
references yet.
You got to find people that
will trust you with a new technology.
But once you're bigger and we're there,
we're referencing, we're using our existing references
to help our new potential prospects
trust that we can solve their problems.
How old are you now?
I would have guessed like 40.
But real quick though, I'm in my twenties.
Your last message to somebody in their twenties
trying to build a billion dollar company in
today's world.
They want to become successful like you.
Give them one more nugget about business.
One more piece of advice.
Your last message to the
younger generation trying to become successful.
Surround yourself with a great team.
It all comes down to people.
You will never do this by yourself.
Yeah.
Find the right team, get the right people
around you, and then go after a great problem.
You got to have a big enough market problem
to get to a billion dollar business for sure.
But you got to have the right team.
How did you identify a billion dollar problem?
I had been in this space a
long time, been around security for big companies.
So we had seen a lot
of what worked and what didn't.
And ultimately we saw things emerging that
looked like they could be big problems.
And look, I will tell you the truth.
This problem, this space has gotten
bigger than we ever thought it would.
So some of it is sometimes
markets evolve in ways you can't predict.
And it's actually made our space even more attractive.
But we knew it'd be a good space.
It's become a great space.
Do you believe in God?
I don't just believe in him, I follow him.
Did you always believe in God?
Yes, I did.
Talk to me about how important faith has
been for you building a billion dollar company.
Well, to me, it's been a great space.
To me, the faith thing has
a number of aspects in my life.
It means partly because I
felt like Jesus lived this way.
I value all the people in my life.
They don't have to join me in my faith view.
They don't have to be having
the same belief system as me.
But I want to care about them, right?
Jesus famously said, do unto others the
way you'd like them to do unto you.
Treat others the way you'd like to be treated.
Well, if you live that way, you're
going to have a pretty good life.
You're going to treat people the
way they want to be treated.
They're going to feel good.
They're going to feel valued.
So that's core.
And I think the other part of the faith
thing is kind of, to use an overused term maybe,
what's your identity?
My identity is not in being
a business guy or an entrepreneur, right?
My identity is being a child of God.
But I happen to be an entrepreneur.
I'm also a husband and a father and a
bunch of other things that are super important to me.
But at the end of the day, I'm not going
to base my worth on whether my business works or not.
I'm happy that it's been great.
The Lord blessed me a lot
in our business, blessed our people.
But at the end of the
day, that's not how I value myself.
The business could go away tomorrow and I'd be okay.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Well, thanks.
It was fun chatting with you.
I really appreciate that.
Guys, this video was incredible.
Austin just went crazy.
With the billion dollar moguls out here.
But I need you guys to like and subscribe
for amazing content we've got coming every single week.
Because I'm going all over the world to interview the
biggest business owners and the most successful people for you all.
And do yourself a favor.
Go down to the link in the description of this video to
join the number one community for business owners in the entire world.
The School of Mentors.
Because every single week, I bring in the multi-millionaires and
billionaires that I interview to mentor you on live calls.
Where you can learn skill sets directly from them.
And the blueprints that they use to become millionaire.
Billionaire entrepreneurs.
So you can do the same.
I can't wait to see you on
the inside of the School of Mentors.
And with that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.